scr.hu 2016-12-25

# SHUt & Share your best gaming moments

#### 1. Some legal stuff to read

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of SHU sp z o.o. ("SHU"), the websites located at screenshu.com and screenhunters.com, mobile and facebook applications. 

#### 2. What types of Information do we collect?

The types of information that we collect fall under two general categories personally identifiable information (PII) and non-personally identifiable information (non-PII). PII consists of any information which can be used to specifically identify you as an individual, whereas non-PII consists of aggregate information or any information that does not reveal your identity. The following sections describe how your PII and non-PII are collected by us, and how we use such information. 

#### 3. How do we collect and use information?

Log Files. Any time you access the Service, our servers automatically gather information from your browser or device. This information includes your IP addresses and browser type (if you are using a browser), device ID, location (if you have enabled this feature), Internet service provider (ISP) or wireless service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Service, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We do not share this information externally. 

#### 4. How do we use cookies?

We use "cookies" to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting our website or using the Service. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to our website and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save user preferences and track user trends. We rely on cookies for the proper operation of our Service; therefore if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the Service will not function properly with your browser. Users who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality in the Service. 

#### 5. Website and applications analytics

We use third-party analytics service providers ("Analytics Providers"), such as Google, Mixpanel, and Flurry, to help us analyze how users use the Service. We may change the Analytics Providers that we use from time to time. The information generated by your browser or device about your use of the Service will be transmitted to and stored by the Analytics Provider(s) on servers in the United States. The Analytics Providers will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Service, compiling reports on website or mobile activity for our use and providing other services relating to Service activity and Internet usage. The Analytics Providers may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on the Analytics Providers’ behalf. By using the Service, you consent to the processing of data about you by the Analytics Provider in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

#### 6. Information about the user

When you register for the Service, we collect a variety of information about you to complete your online profile. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose your PII to other users of the Service. If you choose to connect your SHU account with Facebook or any other service, we will receive and retain basic account registration data you provide to that service, such as name, email address, user ID and profile page URL. We may also receive and display content relevant to your use of the Service from activity feeds or other information from Facebook and other linked services, including the contents of your "Wall," status updates, comments, photos and location "check-ins" to the extent you grant us access to such information from those services. 

#### 7. E-mail address

We require an email address from you when you register for the Service. We use your email both for transactional purposes (e.g., activity updates such as notices that another user is now following you on the Service) and for promotional purposes (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, event notifications, special third-party offers). Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails, including whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you would rather not receive promotional emails from us, please contact us. We reserve the right to send you certain communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We may also contact you by text message (including to any wireless number you may provide to us) solely in connection with the Service. If you would rather not receive text messages from us, you may change or delete your number from your "Account Settings" page, or ask to be removed from our contact list if you receive a call or text message from us. 

#### 8. Demographic data

Demographic data is also collected by the Service. We use this data to tailor our visitors' experience, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. Some of this information may be shared with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable basis. 

#### 9. User's friends information

We offer contact importer tools to help you upload your friends' addresses so that you can find your friends on the Service, and invite your contacts who do not have SHU accounts to join. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts' information. We will send your designated contacts one or more email messages containing your name and inviting them to participate in the Service, which may include follow-up or reminder messages. These emails will also include instructions on how to remove their information from our database. 

#### 10. Data from website's surveys

We may periodically conduct voluntary member surveys. We encourage our members to participate in such surveys because they provide us with important information regarding the improvement of the Service. You may also volunteer for certain surveys that we may offer to our users, and any additional rules regarding the conduct of such surveys will be disclosed to you prior to your participation. 

#### 11. Public forums

We make discussion areas available to our Service’s users and visitors. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any PII. 

#### 12. Third parties - disclosure of user's information

Disclosure Authorized or Required By Law. You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if 

  1. we believe in good faith that we are authorized or required to do so by law, or
  2. you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information; or
  3. we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary or appropriate to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law); (2) protect or defend the rights or property of SHU or a third party; or (3) protect someone's health or safety.

#### 13. Disclosure to trusted third parties by us

We may share your non-PII with third parties, but not in a manner that would reveal your identity. For example, when you access a page on our website, a cookie may be automatically set by us or by our service providers to recognize your browser as you navigate on the Internet and to present you with information and advertising based on your apparent interests. We may share your PII, sometimes in conjunction with your non-PII, with service providers that may be associated with us to perform functions on our behalf. For example, outsourced customer support agents or technology infrastructure providers may need access to your information to perform services for you. Your information will be treated as private and confidential by such service providers and not used for any other purpose than we authorize. In addition, from time to time, we may share PII (such as email or mailing address) about our user base with carefully selected third parties, so they can offer goods and services that we believe may be of interest to our users. If you do not wish to receive offers from our trusted partners, you can change your email preferences at any time by entering Settings section on the website. Information Transferred As a Result of Sale of Business. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets and, depending on the transaction, your PII may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your PII may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your PII is collected or used. 

#### 14. Third-party advertising

We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on the Service on behalf of SHU or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is completely anonymous. Some of these third-party advertising agencies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers you the option to opt out of ad targeting from its member agencies by following the procedures listed at Networkadvertising.org We will only share your information with third parties in the ways defined in this Privacy Policy. 

#### 15. User's age restrictions

Our age restrictions for the Service are set forth in our Terms of Use. We do not target any portion of our Service to children under the age of 13. 

#### 16. Geographic Restrictions

Our services are intended for use by any country’s residents at this time, and the information collected in connection with the Service (including PII) is stored and processed in France. Users may not access, use, or register for the Service if prohibited by law in their country of residence. 

#### 17. Security & Protection

We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer or mobile device and our servers. However, no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure, so we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional interception or misuse. 

#### 18. Links to other websites

We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that may be linked to our Service or of any third party advertisers. 

#### 19. Updating user's information

You may change your email address, password and other information from the "Account Settings" page accessible via a link from our website and mobile application. To the extent you choose to include PII or other information in your profile, the Service allows you to update or remove that information by editing or deleting the content. 

#### 20. Contact SHU

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Service, or your dealings with us, you can contact contact@screenshu.com 

#### 21. Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of any of our Services is subject to this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. BY USING ANY PORTION OF OUR SERVICE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE. 

#### 22. Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that is collected is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our privacy policy from time-to-time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the Service or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use the Service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy. 

#### 23. Revision date

This privacy statement was last revised on January 1, 2016.
